Believe the Impossible. Discover the Incredible.
Journey 2: The Mysterious Island is a adventure, action,
science fiction film directed by Brad Peyton.
Sean Anderson partners with his mom's boyfriend on a mission to find his
grandfather, who is thought to be missing on a mythical island.
Hank Parsons, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Sean Anderson, played by Josh Hutcherson.
Kailani Laguatan, played by Vanessa Hudgens.
Gabato Laguatan, played by Luis Guzmán.
Alexander Anderson, played by Michael Caine.
Elizabeth Parsons, played by Kristin Davis.
Journey 2: The Mysterious Island is a 2012 American science fantasy action-adventure film serving as a standalone sequel to Journey to the Center of the Earth
(2008), and based on Jules Verne's novel The Mysterious Island (1875); like its predecessor, Verne's novel exists within the film's universe.
Directed by Brad Peyton from a script by Brian and Mark Gunn, it stars Dwayne Johnson,
Michael Caine, Josh Hutcherson, Vanessa Hudgens, Luis Guzmán, and Kristin Davis.
The story follows Sean Anderson who, after receiving a distress call from his long-lost grandfather, mounts a rescue
to a mysterious island with help from his militaristic stepfather and the crew of a helicopter tour.
Journey 2: The Mysterious Island was released in
theaters on February 10, 2012, by Warner Bros.
It received mixed reviews, but was a box office success with a
worldwide gross of $335 million, surpassing its predecessor.
The film explores themes of mission, giant lizard,
missing person, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is thought_provoking.